localmotors.com 2018-10-27

# Privacy Policy · Local Motors

## Local Motors Privacy Policy

Local Motors, Inc., and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (herein, “Local  
Motors”) recognizes that its customers, visitors, users (e.g., designers, contributors),  
and others (known collectively or individually as “Users”) who use localmotors.com  
(the “Website”) value their privacy. This “Privacy Policy” applies to all of the  
products, services, and Websites offered by Local Motors, and details important  
information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the  
Website. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the  
Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Local Motors  
Terms of Use. Please note that any comment or other content you post on the  
Website, for example on comment pages, or on the forums, becomes published  
content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this  
Privacy Policy. Your messages and other information you make available in public  
areas of the Website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or  
controlled by Local Motors, and may be used by others to contact you. Local Motors’  
Privacy Policy applies only to websites and services that are owned and operated  
by Local Motors. While other websites may be displayed as links from within Local  
Motors, those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different  
privacy policies. When linking from Local Motors to other websites, if you have  
privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

1\. What information is collected?  
2\. How is your information used, shared and disclosed?  
3\. What about cookies, logs and web beacons?  
4\. Local Motors cares about confidentiality, security, and data integrity.  
5\. You can edit and delete your account information at any time.  
6\. Are you an international user?  
7\. What if we change or update this privacy policy?  
8\. When was this privacy policy last modified?  
9\. Please contact us!

##### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

Generally Local Motors does not require that you register in order to view its  
products, designs, or User comments. Registration is required to use certain  
features such as posting comments, evaluating submissions, participating in the  
forums, submitting designs and participating in competitions. Local Motors and our  
third party service providers may collect personal information when you register with  
Local Motors, when you visit the Website, when you make a purchase, or any time  
you provide information to Local Motors about yourself, including, publicly available  
contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender,  
company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical  
addresses (collectively, “Personal Information”). For example, when you register, we  
ask for information such as your name, email address, and other  
personally-identifying information. In addition, Local Motors and our third party  
service providers may gather or automatically receive and record other  
non-personally-identifying information (“Non-Personal Information”) on server logs  
from your browser even if you do not register with Local Motors, for example, your  
IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit.  
Local Motors and our third party service providers may combine information about  
you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other  
companies.  
Local Motors is committed to protecting the privacy of children under the age of 13.  
Local Motors does not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online  
from children under the age of 13. If Local Motors learns that personally identifiable  
information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Website  
without verified parental consent, then Local Motors will take the appropriate steps  
to delete this information.

##### 2\. HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED, SHARED AND DISCLOSED?

Local Motors and our third party service providers use your Personal Information  
and Non-Personal Information for the following general purposes: to customize the  
advertising and content you see; fulfill your requests for products and services;  
improve our services; contact you with service and other announcements,  
administrative messages and for marketing purposes; conduct research; analytics  
purposes; and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Local  
Motors does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information with other people or  
non-affiliated companies except for the general purposes above, when we have  
your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
(i) We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with  
Local Motors under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your  
Personal Information to help Local Motors communicate with you about offers from  
Local Motors and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have  
any independent right to share this information.  
(ii) We may share Personal Information if we have a good faith belief that access,  
use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a)  
satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental  
request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential  
violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or  
technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or  
safety of Local Motors, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
(iii) We may use both your Personal Information and certain Non-Personal  
Information, and may share it with our third party service providers, for purposes of  
understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements,  
promotions, and/or functionality on the Website.  
(iv) We may use both your Personal Information and certain Non-Personal  
Information, and may share it with our third party service providers, to improve the  
quality and design of the Website, to communicate with Users (through the Website,  
other websites, email, or otherwise), and to create new features, promotions,  
functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User activities,  
preferences and trends.  
(v) We may share Personal Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or  
other forms of legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend  
against legal claims.  
(vi) We may share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to  
investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud,  
situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations  
of Local Motors’ Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.  
(vii) We may transmit Personal Information if Local Motors is acquired by or merged  
with another company. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency,  
reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we may not  
be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.  
Please note that our third party service providers are owned and operated by others,  
and they may have different privacy policies, not subject to our control.  
Please also keep in mind that any Personal Information, designs, or comments that  
you voluntarily disclose on the Website, for example on comment pages, or on the  
forums, becomes publicly available. Designs submitted towards contests will enable  
the public to view your submission; moreover, designs submitted towards profile  
pages will also be viewable by the public. Your account name is displayed to other  
Users when you send and/or post messages through the Website.

##### 3\. WHAT ABOUT COOKIES, LOGS, AND WEB BEACONS?

Local Motors may set and access Local Motors cookies on your computer. You may  
disable these cookies within your browser, but some portions of the Website may  
require that your Local Motors cookies be enabled. When you use Local Motors  
services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends  
whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as  
your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the  
date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify  
your browser. Local Motors may present links in a format that enables us to keep  
track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve  
the quality of our site including offering customized content and advertising. This  
Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by  
Local Motors. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results  
or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own  
cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information  
from you. Local Motors lets other companies that show advertisements on some of  
our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of  
their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or  
other companies do not have access to Local Motors’ cookies. Local Motors may  
use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to Users, to let us know whether  
and when the email was opened. No Personal Information is transmitted through  
web beacons.

##### 4\. LOCAL MOTORS CARES ABOUT CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY, AND DATA  
INTEGRITY.

Because Local Motors is committed to preserving the confidentiality, integrity and  
security of your Personal Information, we have implemented commercially  
reasonable technical safeguards to help us accomplish the same. We cannot,  
however, ensure or warrant the confidentiality, integrity or security of any Personal  
Information, or that Local Motor’s safeguards will prevent the loss or alteration of  
your Personal Information, that you transmit to Local Motors, and you do so at your  
own risk. We use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to Personal  
Information about you to our employees, contractors, and agents who we believe  
reasonably need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products  
or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Local Motors processes Personal  
Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with  
this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We take  
reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we process is accurate,  
complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their  
Personal Information whenever necessary. In no event will Local Motors be  
responsible or liable for the deletion, correction, destruction, damage, loss or failure  
to store any Personal Information. Please note that our third party service providers  
are owned and operated by others, and they may have different safeguards in place  
to preserve the confidentiality, integrity and security of Personal Information, that are  
not subject to our control.

##### 5\. YOU CAN EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ANY TIME.

We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and services to you,  
including those described above. Information associated with your account will be  
kept until your account is deleted, unless we no longer need the data to provide  
products and services.  
You can review and edit your Local Motors account information at any time by  
visiting your account profile page. We reserve the right to use and share your  
Personal Information as provided for herein, but you may opt out and deactivate and  
delete your Local Motors account at any time by canceling your account on the  
account profile page. When you use Local Motors’ services, we make good faith  
efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information and either to correct  
this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise  
required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual  
users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed,  
corrected or removed before processing such requests.

##### 6\. ARE YOU AN INTERNATIONAL USER?

If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any  
other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and  
disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your  
continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy  
as incorporated in our Terms of Use, you will be transferring your Personal  
Information into the United States and you consent to that transfer.

##### 7\. WHAT IF WE CHANGE OR UPDATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

Local Motors may update this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion and  
without prior notice. We will strive to notify you about significant changes in the way  
we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address  
specified in your Local Motors account and/or by placing a notice on the Website.  
We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are  
significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services,  
email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will  
be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior  
versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

##### 8\. WHEN WAS THIS PRIVACY POLICY LAST MODIFIED?

This Privacy Policy was last modified April 13, 2015.

##### 9\. PLEASE CONTACT US!

Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy,  
including Local Motors’ treatment of Personal Information or Local Motors’ third  
party service providers, by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at:  
privacypolicy@local-motors.com .
